# Azfar Saleem **Content Writer**

A highly organised and efficient Content Writer whose efforts have yielded significant results from tasks at hand. With nearly 6 years of experience in writing persuasive Content Writing I believe I can become a valuable asset to the company I have applied to.

# **Work Experience**

April 2021 -Present

**Technology Content** Strategist @ VIDIZMO LLC

As a Technology Content Strategist, I am expected to conduct heavy research about current trends of the Enterprise **Video Content Management Systems** and write blogs that increase our websites traffic, while providing prospective customers vital information about the different systems of this market and its current news.

April 2021

September 2017 - Digital Marketing Manager @ IKnowMyToys

> Managing an effective team of graphic designers, content writers and social media associates I was able to instruct and guide my team towards increasing sales, engagement of customers with social media updates and the reach of their social updates regarding world-renowned toy brands that they provided to customers in Pakistan. With such responsibilities, I got a wholesome perspective into how effective marketing campaigns are made.

September 2016-September 2017

#### **Affiliate Marketing Associate** @ Gaditek

Responsible to build strong relationships with gaming influencers who could help promote a product of the company. This product is called "Kill Ping". Excellent writing skills were required for this position, as I was asked to contact such influencers via social media and email often. To persuade them to assist us, which led us to marketing the product effectively.

## Personal Data

Name - Azfar Bilal Saleem Birth - 19th September 1994 Position - Technology Content Strategist City- Karachi, Sindh Mobile - +923352070555 WhatsApp - +923352070555

### Education

August 2013 -June 2016

Kingston University London - BA(Hons.)

Media and Cultural Studies - Upper Second Class